A Guide to The University of Virginia Hospital Auxiliary Collection 1908-2014
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library, University of Virginia
The University of Virginia Hospital Auxiliary Collection (Hospital Circle) 1908-2013
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library, University of Virginia
MS-13
12.5 linear ft. (19 boxes, ca. 666 items)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Material transferred from Special Collections, Alderman Library, University of Virginia in 1982. Collection was originally received by Special Collections from the University of Virginia Hospital Circle. Later donations include those from Lynda Dunn and Maggie Van Winkle.
Biographical/Historical Information
The University of Virginia Hospital Auxiliary began in 1908 as the University of Virginia Hospital Circle of the King's Daughters. The Constitution and bylaws of that year state that the purpose of the Circle "is to render services to the University of Virginia Hospital." Five standing committees for work and supplies, delicacies, visiting, entertainments, and memberships were created and each committee was required to submit written reports at meetings. Meetings were held in Madison Hall on the first Thursday of each month from October through June with annual dues of $1.20. Meetings proceeded according to Robert's Rules of Order. Members of two years standing were allowed to nominate two new members each year and the group would vote whether or not to accept these members. Membership was limited to 36 active members and unlimited honorary members.
In 1924, Hospital Superintendent Dr. Hornsby, met with medical staff wives to discuss the creation of a larger service organization in order to meet the growing needs of the Hospital. A meeting was held, 150 women from the community offered their services, and The Hospital League was organized. Standing committees were established in the following areas: Publicity, Library, Home Visiting, Hospital Visiting, Flowers, and a Motor Corps. One of the League's most successful fundraising efforts was the creation of the Monticello Cook Book, containing old family recipes.
In their 1926 Constitution, the University of Virginia Hospital Circle dropped the term "of the King's Daughters" from their name, and amended their bylaws so that their purpose was "to render services to the University of Virginia Hospital, primarily to the free wards." The membership cap was lifted and membership was offered to "women of the community who are actively interested in the affairs of the Hospital," with two classes of membership established, active voting members and associate members who could not vote. As the recently established Hospital League assumed a large share of the services that the Hospital Circle had started, the Hospital Circle sought a new area of involvement. In October 1928, the Hospital Circle underwrote the salary of a Hospital Social Worker for one year at a cost of $100.00 per month. This position filled a genuine need at the Hospital and after the first year, the Hospital Social Worker's salary became part of the hospital's operating budget while the Hospital Circle continued to donate funds to support social work at the Hospital. Increased fund-raising projects included tours of historic homes, and a County Jamboree held at Fry's Spring Hall in 1935.
In 1941, Mrs. Mulholland, President of the Hospital League, suggested that the two organizations could work most effectively if they united as one group, at the same time freeing some members up for war work. To enable an efficient merger, the League expressed their willingness to accept the name, dues, budget, officers, and meeting place of the Circle. The two organizations joined together with one membership class of volunteers working to support the needs of the Hospital.
After the war, Mrs. Mulholland visited friends in New York and Philadelphia who were working in a new hospital group called the Pink Ladies. Their membership was recruited from Women's Hospital Auxiliaries in hospitals belonging to the National Hospital Association. She returned to Virginia and in 1951 organized a local chapter, recruiting 115 women from 40 organizations. One of the first jobs of the Pink Ladies was the sale of sandwiches to family and friends of patients in the waiting rooms. Ward carts allowed patients to purchase needed items and the gift and baby shops soon grew into substantial businesses.
In 1952 the Hospital Circle was reorganized as the Hospital Auxiliary in order to secure the benefits of state and national affiliation. The Hospital Auxiliary and Pink Lady personnel joined together as one organization, coordinating all volunteer activities in the Hospital. In 1985, the Hospital Auxiliary was incorporated to become the University of Virginia Hospital Auxiliary, Inc. with the purpose of rendering "service to the University of Virginia Hospital and its patients through ways approved or proposed by the Administration of the Hospital."
In its earliest days the Hospital Circle provided delicacies such as oranges, ice cream, and custards to ward patients and members sewed children's gowns, ether jackets and hot water bag covers for the wards. In 1911 the Hospital Circle contributed to the purchase of an X-ray machine for the hospital. Through the years of its existence, the Hospital Circle supported the work of the hospital's Social Service Department, raised funds to help the hospital purchase needed medical equipment, provided recreation and "Pinky Puppets" for children, supplied flowers to the wards, and made donations to the Nursing Scholarship Fund and the Drug Fund. Now, as in the past, the ethic of service to the Hospital holds strong. Venture Awards are given out annually to support programs that "benefit patients, patients' families or in some way improve service to the Medical Center community." The 2003 Venture Awards will provide a total of $20,000.00 to qualified applicants. Past recipients include the Malcolm Cole Child Care Center, the Cancer Center, and the Alex Sawyer Hospitality House. The hospital gift shop provides a much needed service and supports the fund-raising efforts of the Auxiliary. The Auxiliary also hosts book fairs and the annual Lights of Love ceremony, offers newborn baby photos and t-shirts, provides patient representatives to assist patients and their families, supports scholarship funds, and stays abreast of relevant information on health matters through their Legislative Committee. Numerous volunteers from the Hospital Auxiliary can be found throughout the hospital providing support to patients and families on a daily basis. Today's University of Virginia Hospital Auxiliary, Inc. carries on with pride the tradition of service to the Hospital that began with the University of Virginia Hospital Circle.
Scope and Content
The collection includes regular and executive board minutes, financial statements, social services files, Annual Reports, and scrapbooks of photographs and miscellaneous materials.
Arrangement
Arranged by minutes, annual reports, financial reports, correspondence and other archival material. Later additions arranged by date.
Contents List
- MINUTE BOOK, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1908-1912, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 001-001)
  CONTAINS ANNUAL REPORTS, CONSTITUTION AND BYLAWS
- MINUTE BOOK, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1914-1935, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 001-002)
  CONTAINS REPORTS; TAX FORM; MEMBERSHIP LIST; LETTER DATED FEBRUARY 22, 1932, FROM H.R. PRATT OF THE VIRGINIA PLAYERS REGARDING THE FINANCES OF THE PRODUCTION OF THE "MERCHANT OF VENICE"; BROADSIDE ADVERTISING THE HOSPITAL LEAGUE EVENING PROGRAM OF TONY SARG'S MARIONETTES ON JANUARY 12, 1928; PROGRAM FOR "RUTH DRAPER" ON FRIDAY, NOVEMBER 11 (1921? 1927? 1932? 1938?), SPONSORED BY THE HOSPITAL LEAGUE
- MINUTE BOOK, CONSTITUTION & BYLAWS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1926-1940, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 001-003)
  CONTAINS CONSTITUTION AND BY LAWS AND THE PROGRAM FOR "FOUR ORIGINAL PLAYS AND AN INTERLUDE" PRESENTED BY THE HOSPITAL CIRCLE ON APRIL 12 AND 13, 1937
- MINUTE BOOK, REGULAR MEETINGS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1940/09-1945/06, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 001-004)
- MINUTE BOOK, EXECUTIVE BOARD, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1942/09-1945/02, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 001-005)
- MINUTE BOOK, EXECUTIVE BOARD, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1945/09-1953/05, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 001-006)
- MINUTE BOOK, REGULAR MEETINGS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1945/10-1949/01, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 001-007)
- MINUTE BOOK, REGULAR MEETINGS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1949/02-1952/05, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 002-001)
- MINUTE BOOK, EXECUTIVE BOARD, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1953-1957, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 002-002)
- MINUTE BOOK, ANNUAL REPORTS, EXECUTIVE AND REGULAR, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1957/05-1965/05, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 002-003)
  CONTAINS ANNUAL REPORTS 1963-1965
- MINUTE BOOK, ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1965/06-1966/05, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 002-004)
  CONTAINS ANNUAL REPORT 1966
- MINUTE BOOK, ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY BOARD 1966/06-1967/05, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 002-005)
  CONTAINS ANNUAL REPORT 1967
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1967/05-1971/12, TMs (Box-folder 003-001)
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY BOARD 1967/06-1968/05, TMs (Box-folder 003-002)
  CONTAINS ANNUAL REPORT 1968
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY BOARD 1968/05-1972/04, TMs (Box-folder 003-003)
  CONTAINS ANNUAL REPORTS, FINANCIAL STATEMENTS
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1972/02-1974/12, TMs (Box-folder 003-004)
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1975/01-1976/12, TMs (Box-folder 003-005)
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1977/01-1978/12, TMs (Box-folder 003-006)
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1979/01-1980/12, TMs (Box-folder 003-007)
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1981/01-1982/12, TMs (Box-folder 003-008)
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1983/01-1984/12, TMs (Box-folder 003-009)
- MINUTES AND BY-LAWS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1985/01-1986/05, TMs (Box-folder 003-010)
- TREASURER'S RECORDS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1937-1952, TMs (Box-folder 004-001)
- LEDGER, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1947-1951, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 004-002)
- TREASURER'S RECORDS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1947-1956, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 004-003)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1954/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-004)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1955/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-005)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1956/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-006)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1957/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-007)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1958/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-008)
- TREASURER'S REPORTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1958/05-1959/04, TMs (Box-folder 004-009)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1959/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-010)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1960/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-011)
- TREASURER'S REPORTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1959/05-1960/04, AMs/TMs (Box-folder 004-012)
- TREASURER'S REPORTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1960/05/01-1961/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-013)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1961/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-014)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1962/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-015)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1963/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-016)
- CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1964/04/20, TMs (Box-folder 004-017)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1965/04/19, TMs (Box-folder 004-018)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1966/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-019)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1967/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-020)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1972/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-021)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY PROPOSED BUDGET 1972/05/01 - 1973/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-022)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1973/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-023)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY PROPOSED BUDGET 1973/05/01 - 1974/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-024)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1974/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-025)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY PROPOSED BUDGET 1974/05/01 - 1975/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-026)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1975/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-027)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY PROPOSED BUDGET 1975/05/01 - 1976/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-028)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1976/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-029)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY PROPOSED BUDGET 1976/05/01 - 1977/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-030)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1977/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-031)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY PROPOSED BUDGET 1977/05/01 - 1978/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-032)
- STATEMENT OF CASH RECEIPTS AND DISBURSEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1978/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-033)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY PROPOSED BUDGET 1978/05/01 - 1979/04/30, TMs (Box-folder 004-034)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1984/04-1985/07, TMs (Box-folder 005-001)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1985/08-1986/10, TMs (Box-folder 005-002)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1986/11-1988/02, TMs (Box-folder 005-003)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1988/03-1988/12, TMs (Box-folder 005-004)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1989/01-1990/02, TMs (Box-folder 005-005)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1990/03-1991/04, TMs (Box-folder 005-006)
- BUDGET, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1991/05-1992/04, TMs (Box-folder 005-007)
- BUDGET, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1992/05-1993/04, TMs (Box-folder 005-008)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1993 (April), TMs (Box-folder 005-009)
- SOCIAL SERVICE DEPARTMENT FILES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL 1926-1940, AMs/TMs (Box-folder 006-001)
  CONTAINS CORRESPONDENCE
- SOCIAL SERVICES DEPARTMENT FILES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL 1940-1941, TMs (Box-folder 006-002)
- SOCIAL SERVICES DEPARTMENT FILES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL 1933-1941, TMs (Box-folder 006-003)
- SOCIAL SERVICES DEPARTMENT FILES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL 1926-1939, TMs (Box-folder 006-004)
  CONTAINS CORRESPONDENCE, NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS, PAMPHLETS
- SOCIAL SERVICES DEPARTMENT FILES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL 1931-1939, AMs/TMs (Box-folder 006-005)
- SOCIAL SERVICES DEPARTMENT FILES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL 1930-1938, TMs (Box-folder 006-006)
- AN INFORMAL HISTORY OF THE SOCIAL SERVICE DEPARTMENT BY MRS. CARROLL MASON SPARROW 1939, TMs (Box-folder 006-007)
  READ BEFORE THE HOSPITAL CIRCLE AT ITS MEETING, JANUARY 5, 1939
- UVA LIBRARY RECORDS OF DONATION AND ACCEPTANCE, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY COLLECTION 1949-1973, TMs (Box-folder 006-008)
- PLAYBILL FOR GHOSTS AND THE MASTER BUILDER 1922/03, PAMPHLET (Box-folder 006-009)
  BENEFIT PERFORMANCE
- MEMBERSHIP LISTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1961-1966, TMs (Box-folder 006-010)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY HOSPITALITY HOUSE BROCHURE N.D., BROCHURE (Box-folder 006-011)
- REPORT FOR THE YEAR 1951-52, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1951-1952, TMS (Box-folder 007-001)
- CARTS AND GIFT SHOP, ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL CIRCLE 1955-1956, TMs (Box-folder 007-002)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1959/06, TMs (Box-folder 007-003)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1960/06, TMs (Box-folder 007-004)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1962/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-005)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1963/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-006)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1964/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-007)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1965/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-008)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1966/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-009)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1967/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-010)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1968/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-011)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1969/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-012)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1970/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-013)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1971/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-014)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1972/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-015)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1973/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-015.1)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1974/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-016)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1975/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-016.1)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1976/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-016.2)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1977/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-017)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1978/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-018)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1979/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-019)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1980/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-019.1)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1981/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-020)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1982/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-020.1)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1983/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-020.2)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1984/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-020.3)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1986/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-020.5)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1987/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-020.6)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1988/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-021)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1989/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-022)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1990/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-023)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1991/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-024)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1992/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-024.1)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1993/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-024.2)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1994/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-024.3)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1995/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-024.4)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1996/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-024.5)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1997/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-025)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1998/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-026)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1999/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-027)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2000/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-028)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2001/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-029)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2002/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-030)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2003/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-031)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2004/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-032)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2005/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-033)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY, 1949-61 1949-1961, scrapbook (Box-folder 008-001)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1952-1954, scrapbook (Box-folder 008-002)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1951-1954, scrapbook (Box-folder 008-003)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1951-1954, scrapbook (Box-folder 008-003)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1952-1957, scrapbook (Box-folder 008-004)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1956-1960, scrapbook (Box-folder 008-005)
- SCRAPBOOK/PHOTO ALBUM, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY ca. 1956-1961, scrapbook (Box-folder 008-006)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1958-1961, scrapbook (Box-folder 009-001)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1958-1964, scrapbook (Box-folder 009-002)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1964-1965, scrapbook (Box-folder 009-003)
- SCRAPBOOK, BOB HOPE SHOW, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1966, scrapbook (Box-folder 009-004)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1962-1968, scrapbook (Box-folder 009-005)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1969-1972, scrapbook (Box-folder 010-001)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1973-1975, scrapbook (Box-folder 010-002)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1976-1977, scrapbook (Box-folder 010-003)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1978-1979, scrapbook (Box-folder 010-004)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1980-1981, scrapbook (Box-folder 011-001)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1982-1983, scrapbook (Box-folder 011-002)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1983-1985, scrapbook (Box-folder 011-003)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1985-1987, scrapbook (Box-folder 012-001)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1987-1989, scrapbook (Box-folder 012-002)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1996-1997, scrapbook (Box-folder 013-001)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL JUNIOR AUXILIARY 1963-1970, scrapbook (Box-folder 014-001)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL JUNIOR AUXILIARY 1993-1995, scrapbook (Box-folder 014-002)
- SCRAPBOOK, UVA HOSPITAL JUNIOR AUXILIARY 1996-1997, scrapbook (Box-folder 014-003)
- NOTES AND MISCELLANEOUS MATERIAL ON THE HISTORY OF THE HOSPITAL AUXILIARY COLLECTED BY ESTHER GAVURIN 1997, notebook; notes (Box-folder 015)
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1986 (June ) - 1987 (May 21), TMs (Box-folder 016-001)
  Margaret Domnick, Barbara Stenard
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1987 (June 18) - 1988 (May 19), TMs (Box-folder 016-002)
  Barbara Stenard
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1988 (June 16) - 1989 (May 25), TMs (Box-folder 016-003)
  Barbara Stenard, Gay Kulthau
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1989 (June 15) - 1990 (May 24), TMs (Box-folder 016-004)
  Gay Kulthau
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1990 (June 11) - 1991 (May 30), TMs (Box-folder 016-005)